L. C. Dunn Papers ca.1920-1974 Mss.B.D917
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, ca.1920-1974 (Box 1)
  - American Committee for Displaced German Scholars, 1933-1937; Approximately 180 items (Box 1)
    Displaced German scholars; Displaced German Scholars -- Braun, Joachim Werner; Displaced German Scholars -- Goldschmidt, Richard Benedict; Displaced German Scholars -- Gruneberg, Hans; Displaced German Scholars -- Stern, Curt
  - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 1)
    Grove, Mortimer
  - American Genetic Association (Box 1)
  - American Naturalist (Box 1)
  - American Philosophical Society Library, 1961-1972; 8 folders (Box 1)
    Avery, Roy C.
    Bell, Whitfield Jenks, Jr.
    Bodine, J.H.
    Bridenbaugh, Carl
    Caspari, Ernst
    Cleland, Ralph E.
    Cole, Leon J.
    Coleman, William
    Corner, George W.
    Demerec, Milislav
    Duane, Morris
    Fuller, William A.
    Glass, H. Bentley
    Heyn, Anton N.J.
    Hutt, F.B.
    Irwin, M.R.
    Lederberg, Joshua
    Lerner, I. Michael
    Marvanova, Ludmila
    Metzdorf, Robert
    Neel, James V.
    Shryock, Richard Harrison
    Sonnenborn, T.M.
    Sturtevant, A.H.
    Wagner, R.P.
    American Philosophical Society; Committee activities; Davenport, Charles Benedict; Genetics -- Books on genetics; History of biology, especially genetics; Preservation of historical materials; Shull, George Harrison
  - American Philosophical Society Seminar, 1967-1969; 2 folders (Box 1)
    American Philosophical Society; Bibliographical matters; History of biology, especially genetics
  - American Review of Soviet Medicine (Box 1)
    Heiman, Jacob
  - American Review on the Society (Box 1)
    Union (Yearbook)
  - American Russian Institute (Box 1)
    Collins, Henry H. Jr.
  - American Society of Human Genetics (Box 1)
  - American Society of Naturalists (Box 1)
    Cattell, Jaques
  - American-Soviet Friendship Council, 1944-1948; 2 folders (Box 1)
    Executive Board Minutes
    Science Committee Minutes
    Committee activities; Russian politics and science; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs
  - American-Soviet Science Society, 1945-1947; 3 folders (Box 2)
    Bara, Walter A.
    Chertak, Dorothy
    Dresden, Arnold
    Goussev, Anatole
    Harmer, Walter J.
    Harris, Helen
    Hubbard, C.J.
    Jacobs, Jane
    Juhn, Mary
    Kaempffert, Waldemar
    Lamont, Corliss
    Langmuir, Irving
    Lefschetz, A.
    Leslie, Robert L.
    Lessells, John M.
    MacInnes, D.A.
    Moore, Marston
    Morford, Richard
    Munsell, Alex
    Muller, H.J.
    Niederhauser, John S.
    Novick, S.
    Oakes, Mervin E.
    Pincus, J.W.
    Snyder, L.H.
    Stanley, W.M.
    Thompson, James S.
    Thomson, Charles A.
    Vavilov, Sergei
    Waksman, Selman A.
    Zavadovsky, M.M.
    Zlotowski, Ignance
    Publication; Russian politics and science; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs
  - Amos, D. Bernard (Box 2)
    Gruneberg, H.
  - Apgar, Virginia (Box 2)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1960-1972; 18 folders (Box 2)
    Bauer, Robert H.
    Bender, Michael A.
    Burlingame, Anson
    Claus, Walter D.
    Columbia University
    Dinitz, Ira
    Edington, Charles W.
    Goodell, Warren F.
    Goodell, Warren F. Jr.
    Halford, R.S.
    Helmbrecht, Arthur
    Judd, Burke H.
    Laughnan, John R.
    Lewis, James
    MacPherson, George S.
    Martin, C. Paul
    Meyer, Calvin B.
    Meyers, Sheldon
    Miller, Harold N.
    Nelson, Henry K.
    Nevis Biological Station
    Parker, Dean R.
    Potter, Harmon S.
    Schultz, Vincent
    Touchberry, Robert W.
    Underhill, Helen F.
    Walsh, Harry R.
    Yerzley, T.W.
    Atomic Energy Commission; Bibliographical matters; Business; Columbia University; Human evolution, physical anthropology -- Institute for the Study of Human Variation; Mouse genetics; Population genetics; Research support; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Autobiographical notes (Box 2)
  - Avery, Oswald T. (Box 2)
  - Ballard, W.W. (Box 3)
  - Baregozzi (Box 3)
  - Battghia (Box 3)
  - Beadle, George W. (Box 3)
  - Behre, Charles H. (Box 3)
  - Bell, Whitfield J. Jr. (Box 3)
  - Berge, S. (Box 3)
  - Bermies, Gert (Box 3)
  - Bernstein, Felix (Box 3)
    Emergengy Comm. in Aid of Displaced Foreign Scholars Report
    Pegram, George B.
  - Bertalanffy, L. von (Box 3)
  - Biographical Memoirs (reprints) (Box 3)
  - Bissonnette, T. Hume (Box 3)
  - Blakeslee, Albert F. (Box 3)
  - Blanco, Ramon (Box 3)
  - Bleibtrev, Hermann K. "The Impact of Urbanization on Human Evolution" (with Dunn, L.C.) Rome (Jewish Community) (Box 3)
  - Block, Robert (Box 3)
  - Blood Groups - Jews (Box 3)
    Curri, A.N.
  - Blood Study (see also: Dunn. Rome) (Box 3)
    Ceppellini, Ruggerio
    Levine, Philip
    Loghem, J.J. Van
  - Bluhm, Agnes (Box 3)
  - Blyson, Doris (Box 3)
  - Boas, Franz (Box 3)
  - Bohn, W.E. (Box 3)
  - Bonnevie, Kristine, 1930-1938; 36 items (Box 3)
    Harrison, R.G.
    Hayden, P.M.
    McGregor, J.H.
    Nicholas, J.S.
    Rinid, Güdrün
    Bibliographical matters; Embryology, developmental genetics; Lectures, public speaking; Political issues; Population genetics; Publication; World War II -- Impact on science
  - Book Reviews: Future of Man, Error and Deception in Science (Box 3)
  - Booth, Kate H. (Box 3)
  - Booth, Mary E. (Box 3)
  - Bowditch, M. (Box 3)
  - Bowen, Wilbor A. (Box 3)
  - Braun, Werner (Box 3)
  - Braverman, Irwin (Box 3)
  - Brecher, Leonore, 1930-1938; 29 items (Box 3)
    Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Biographical and personal data; Physiology; Research support
  - Bridges, Calvin B., 1932-1940; 40 items (Box 3)
    Cook, R.C.
    Dobszhansky
    Emerson, R.E.
    Gilbert, W.M.
    McCastline, William H.
    Morgan, T.H.
    Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Cytogenetics; Drosophila genetics; Graduate study -- Bridges, Philip; Publication
  - Briggs, L. Cabot (Box 3)
  - British Scientists, 1940; 26 items (Box 3)
    Berle, A.A.
    Cohn, Alfred
    Forbes, William H.
    Huxley, Julian
    Johnson, Alvin
    Laundauer, Walter
    Lothian, Lord
    Miller, Perrie
    Morgan, Thomas H.
    Pappenheimer, Alwin M.
    Pilley, John
    Shapley, Harlow
    Woodruff, L.L.
    Political issues; World War II -- Impact on science
  - Bronk, Detlev W. (Box 3)
  - Buck (Box 3)
  - Buffalo Museum of Science (Box 3)
  - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists (Box 3)
    Hollaender, Alexander
    Lapp, Ralph E.
  - Bush, Vannevar (Box 3)
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray (Box 3)
  - Byers, Vincent G. (Box 3)
  - Calkins, Gary N. (Box 3)
  - Calkins, Helen R. (Box 3)
  - Care (Box 3)
    Mayers, Francis X.
  - Carlson, Elof Axel (Box 3)
  - Carnegie Committee, 1929-39 (Box 3)
    Davenport, Charles B.
    Kidder, A.V.
    Laughlin, H.H.
    Merriam, John C.
  - Carnochan, Fred C. (Box 3)
  - Carrel, Alexis, 1923-1936; 95 items (Box 3)
    Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Biographical and personal data; Cancer, chemotherapy; Poultry genetics; Recommendations -- Ephrussi, Boris; Recommendations -- Schweitzer, Morton
  - Carter, T.C. (Box 3)
  - Caspari, Ernst Wilhelm, 1938-1944; 57 items (Box 4)
    AAAS Grants Comm.
    Hamburger, Victor
    Kunkel, B.W.
    Pearl, Raymond
    Genetics -- Ephestia; Mouse genetics; Publication; Recommendations -- Caspari, Ernst Wilhelm; Research support
  - Castle, E.H. (Box 4)
  - Castle, Edward S. (Box 4)
  - Castle, William Ernest, 1924-1961; 97 items (Box 4)
    Cleland, R.E.
    Cuenot, Lucien
    Curtis, Marjorie R.
    Academic freedom; American Philosophical Society; Bibliographical matters; Biographical and personal data -- Castle, William Ernest; Honors; Mouse genetics; National Academy of Sciences; Poultry genetics; Radiation genetics; Rat genetics; Recommendations
  - Cattell, J. McK. (Box 4)
  - Chalkley, Lyman (Box 4)
  - Chambers, Robert (Box 4)
  - Charles, Donald Randolph, 1930-1955; 22 items (Box 4)
    Cooper, Kenneth
    Biographical and personal data; Educational matters; Mouse genetics; Recommendations
  - Cheng, Dorothy Wei (Box 4)
  - Chesley, Paul RESTRICTED (Permission of L.C.D. or A.P.S. librarian necessary) (Box 4)
  - Churchman, C. West (Box 4)
  - Clarke, H.T. (Box 4)
  - Cleland, Ralph E. (Box 4)
  - Clifford, Richard C. (Box 4)
  - Coalbin Press (Box 4)
  - Codington, John F. (Box 4)
  - Coe, W.R. (Box 4)
  - Cohn, Alfred E. (Box 4)
  - Cole, L.J. (Box 4)
  - Columbia University, 1929-1945; 18 folders (Box 4)
    Columbia University; Committee activities; Educational matters; Fellowships, assistantships; Genetics; Mouse genetics; Political issues; Population genetics; Research support; World War II -- Impact on science
  - Columbia University - Columbia Defense Committee., 1940-41 (Box 5)
    Barker, J.W.
    Fackenthal, Frank D.
    Grant, E.J.
    Rautenstrauch, Walter
  - Columbia University - Convocations, 1943 (Box 5)
    Ayres, Harry Morgan
    Butler, Nicholas M.
    Chamberlain, Joseph P.
    Davis, Malcolm W.
    Gilroy, Katherine M.
    Gromyko, Andrei A.
    Kandel, Isaac L.
    Sayre, E.B.
    Shotwell, James T.
    Smith, Mariana
  - Columbia University - Council for Research in Social Sciences (Box 5)
  - Columbia University - Dean of Science Faculty (Box 5)
    Detwiller, S.R.
    Dodge, M. Haretey
    McBain, Howard Lee
    Neare, Louise
    Woodbridge, F.D.
    Woodbridge, F.J.E.
  - Columbia University - Department of Zoology (Box 5)
  - Columbia University - Fackenthal, F.D., 1942 (Box 5)
    Butler, Nicholas Murray
    Fermi, Enrico
    Hogness, T.R.
    Jessup, P.C.
    Lehmann-Haupt, Helmut
    Tomarkin, L.W.
    Vrey, Harold C.
  - Columbia University - Faculty Fellowship Fund (Box 5)
    Baekeland, L.H.
    Baron, Salo
    Boas, Franz
    Burns, E.M.
    Clark, Jane P.
    Clarke, H.P.
    Coffin, Henry S.
    Collins, Baxter
    Coss, John C.
    Dewey, John
    Dodge, M. Hantey
    Evans, Austin P.
    Fite, E.B.
    Frisch, Karl von
    Gildersleeve, Virginia C.
    Greeg, Alan
    Hagemeister, Paula
    Kandel, I.L.
    Kiewe, Paul
    LaMer, Victor K.
    Meek, Lois Hayden
    Miller, C.P.
    Montague, W.P.
    Murphy, Gardner
    Murrow, E.R.
    Neumann, Gerhardt
    Reed, Mary M.
    Reichard, Gladys A.
    Ritt, J.F.
    Segrè, Angelo
    Simba, Robert
    Smith, Young B.
    Stevens, David H.
    Stewart, Gertrude D.
    Sulzberger, Marion B.
    Wechsler, Albert L.
    Westermann, W.L.
  - Columbia University - Genetics Lab (Box 5)
  - Columbia University - Library Planning Committee (Box 5)
  - Columbia University - Queries (Box 5)
  - Columbia University - Suggested recommendations of the committee on program (Box 5)
  - Columbia University - Teachers College - George S. Counts (Box 5)
  - Community Service Society of New York (Box 5)
  - Conant, J.B. (Box 5)
  - Condon, Edward U (Box 5)
  - Condon Case Material (Box 5)
  - Conklin, Edwin G (Box 5)
  - Connecticut, University of (Box 5)
  - Connecticut Agricultural College Convocation, Jan. 20, 1925 - (Box 5)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Exp. Station and W.L. Slate, 1928-1933; 21 items (Box 5)
    Wallace, Henry A.
    Genetics -- Sheep; National Academy of Sciences; Research support
  - Connell, Frank H. (Box 5)
  - Conversation [Radio Program] (Box 5)
  - Cook, Robert C. (Box 5)
    Journal of Heredity
  - Corner, George Washington (Box 5)
    Dobzhansky, T.
  - to L. C. Dunn, September 17, 1937; Cowley, Malcolm (Box 5)
  - Coyne, Marshall A. (Box 5)
  - Crew, F.A.E. (Box 5)
  - Cumming, C.N. Wentworth (Box 5)
  - Curry, Viola A. (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, 1945-1955; 14 items; Dahlberg, Gunnar, 1893-1956 (Box 5)
    - 1 letter to L. C. Dunn, 1949; Dahlberg, Gandhi
    - 16 letters to and from L. C. Dunn, Dahlberg, Gunnar, 1893-1956
      Biographical and personal data; Human genetics; Population genetics; Recommendations -- Book, Jan
    - to L. C. Dunn, n.d; Dahlberg, Ragna
    - 32 letters to L. C. Dunn, Dahlberg, Stina
    - Photographs
  - Dalton, H. Clark (Box 5)
  - D'Ancona, Umberto (Box 5)
  - Danforth, Charles Haskell, 1928-1952; 45 items (Box 5)
    Columbia University; Fisher, Ronald Aylmer; Mouse genetics
  - Daniel, J.F. (Box 5)
  - Daniel, Janet (Box 5)
  - David, Edward E., Jr. (Box 5)
  - David, Paul R., 1930-1946; 28 items (Box 5)
    Biographical and personal data; Graduate study; Human genetics; Population genetics; Research support
  - Davidson, Jo (Box 5)
  - Davis, Brodley M. (Box 5)
  - Davis, Donald E. (Box 5)
  - Davis, Herbert (Box 5)
  - Deacon, Warren (Box 6)
  - Dean, Geoffrey (Box 6)
  - Dellinger, S.C. (Box 6)
  - Demerec, Milislav, 1936-1951; 25 items (Box 6)
    Conferences and symposia; Editorial matters -- Advances in Genetics; Political issues; Publication
  - Dempster, Everett R. (Box 6)
  - Deschin, Mrs. Jacob (Box 6)
  - Detlefsen, John A. (Box 6)
  - Detwiler, J.D. (Box 6)
  - Detwiler, Samuel R. (Box 6)
  - DiCapua, Guiuseppina (Box 6)
  - Dobrovolskaia-Zavadskaia, N. (Box 6)
  - Dobzhansky, Theodosius, 1936-1951; 353 items (Box 6)
    Albareda, Jose M.
    Amerika
    Angel, J. Lawrence
    Atlantic Monthly
    Babcock, F.B.
    Baitsell, George A.
    Barigozzi, C.
    Beltran, Enrique
    Birdsell, Joseph B.
    Bodenstein, D.
    Boutell, Clip
    Brink, R.A.
    Briquet, Raul Jr.
    Buchenau, Tyler
    Buchholz, J.T.
    Bureau of American Ethnology
    Burkhardt, Elizabeth Z.
    Cardiff, Ira D.
    Cheveskin, Howard
    Churchman, C. West
    Collazo, Ana M. Diaz
    College of Physicians and Surgeons of New York
    Columbia University Press
    Cooney, Tim
    Dartmouth Medical School
    David, Lore R.
    Davis, Kingsley
    Deevey, G.S.
    Dempster, Everett R.
    Dickinson, Berton C.
    Duggan, Stephen
    Dunn, L.C.
    Emerson, A.E.
    Fejos, Paul
    Feldman, M.
    Fisher, Agnes C.
    Flanagan, Dennis
    Forbes, James
    Frankley, Alexander
    Glass, Bentley
    Goldschmidt, Elizabeth
    Goodale, H.D.
    Haas, Otto H.
    Hamburger, Viktor
    Happ, George B.
    Harrar, J.G.
    Henry, Harold
    Herzenberg, Leonard A.
    Howe, Lt. Branch Jr.
    Johnson, Albert G.
    Journal of the History of Medicine
    Keener, Mrs. John D.
    Kerr, Warwick E.
    Krout, John A.
    Landgraf, John L.
    Leonard, Warren H.
    Levitan, Max
    Mendes, Luiz T.
    Moody, Paul A.
    Moriwaki, Daigoro
    Muntzing, Arne
    Negus, Sidney S.
    New American Library
    Novaes, Fernando C.
    Park, Thomas
    Parkinson, N.A.
    Patrick, Ruth
    Persons, Stow
    Plough, H.H.
    Poulson, D.F.
    Proffitt, Charles G.
    Rath, Stephen
    Reheis, George C.
    Ronald Press Company
    Scheinfeld, Amram
    Scientific Monthly
    Serra, J.A.
    Shipman, Margaret
    Simpson, Mrs. Alan
    Singleton, W.R.
    Slatis, Herman M.
    Stebbins, G. Ledyard Jr.
    Stetten, DeWitt
    Stolper, Toni
    Stone, Wilson
    Titterington, E.J.G.
    Uffner, Melville W.
    University of North Carolina
    Wald, George
    Wanscher, J.H.
    Wastock, Irene
    Weeks, Marion E.
    Weinstock, Herbert
    Weiss, Joan M.
    Wilson, E.B.
    Zelle, Max R.
    Zuleta, Julian De
    Anthropology; Biographical and personal data; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Columbia University; Drosophila genetics; Evolution; Human genetics; Invitations; Population genetics; Publication; Recommendations; Research support; Russian politics and science; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; Teaching; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Dodge, B.O. (Box 6)
  - Dollard, Charles (Box 6)
  - Dougherty, Ellsworth C. (Box 6)
  - Dryden, Hugh L. (Box 6)
    Castle, W.E.
  - Dunbar, Carl O. (Box 6)
  - Dunn, A.M. (Box 6)
  - Dunn, Harriet A. (Box 6)
    photos
  - Dunn, L. C. (Leslie Clarence), 1915-1960; 51 folders
    Biographical and personal data; Columbia University; Congratulations, greetings, thanks; Ethical issues; Eugenics; Human genetics; Mouse genetics; Poetry and literature; Political issues; Population genetics; Russian politics and science; Teaching; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
    - Abnormal Hemoglobins,..., Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 6)
    - The American Naturalist in American Biology, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 6)
    - Autobiographical Data, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 6)
    - Birthday Greetings, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 6)
    - Book of Wednesdays, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 6)
    - Developmental Genetics, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 6)
    - Eugenics Notebook, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 6)
    - Genes, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Genetic Lecture Notes, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Genetics in Historical Perspective, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Genetics in the 20th C., Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Genetics of the Domestic Fowl, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Growth of Genetics, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Hecht, Selig, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Heredity, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Heredity and Environment, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Heredity and the Community, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Heredity and the Study of Small Communities, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Human variation, a biologist's view, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Lectures, 1950-1959; 13 folders; Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974
      Blakeslee, Albert Francis; Ethical issues; Evolution; Genetics; Human evolution, physical anthropology; Lectures, public speaking; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
      - Lecture: Aims of Genetics, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
        Aub, Joseph C.
        Levine, Philip R.
      - Lecture: Alcuni Problemi Moderni Intorno All'Eredita, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
      - Lecture: Developmental and Population Genetics of a Complex Locus, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
      - Lecture: Evolutionary Forces Acting on Populations of Wild House Mice, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
      - Lecture: Heredity and Development, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
      - Lecture: Heredity and Politics, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
        Hirsch, Felix E.
        Myers, Rowland M.
      - Lecture: Human Variation, A Biologist's View, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
      - Lecture: In Honor of Albert F. Blakeslee, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
      - Lecture: Lethal Genes and Factors Affecting their Distribution in Populations, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
      - Lecture: Maintenance of Polymorphism, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
        Pollitzer, William
        Robinson, H.F.
        Whittinghill, Maurice
      - Lecture: The Origins of Biological Variety as Seen in the Laboratory Mouse, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
      - Lecture: University of Rochester Meeting, March 4, 1959; Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
      - Lecture: [Used to teach Gen. Biology], Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Mendel, Gregor Johann, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Notebook for Genetics, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Notebook for Lectures, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Notebook "Hist. 1", Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Notebook (Rome), Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Notes, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Notes: Cytology and Embryology, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 7)
    - Passport Correspondence, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 8)
    - Permissions to Publish, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 8)
    - Physiological Genetics, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 8)
    - Poetry and Translations, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 8)
    - Race and Biology, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 8)
      Metraux, Alfred
    - Report to the President of the University of Conn., Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 8)
    - Science and the Future of Society, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 9)
    - Science Under Socialism, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 9)
    - Sheets from Army Notebook, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 9)
    - Soviet Genetics, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 9)
    - Summer in Maine, 1931; Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 9)
    - University of Rochester Meeting, March 4, 1959; Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 9)
    - Variety and Biological Progress, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 9)
    - Wild House Mice, Why do We Collect and Study?, Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 9)
    - Zoology Notes, (1915); Dunn, L. C., (Leslie Clarence), 1893-1974 (Box 9)
  - Dunn, Mrs. Louise (Box 9)
  - Dunn Family materials (Box 9)
  - Dunn-Booth Correspondence (Box 9)
  - Dunn-Hitchcock Family Papers (Box 9)
  - Dunning, Wilhelmina F. (Box 9)
  - Dyson-Hudson, Neville (Box 9)
  - Dyson-Hudson, Mrs. Rada Demerec (Box 9)
  - East, E.M. (Box 9)
  - Edsall, John T. (Box 9)
  - Edwards, Marvin L., 1953-1954; 140 items (Box 9)
    Human genetics; Population genetics; Travel -- Italy; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - Einsele, Wilhelm (Box 9)
    Hodgdon, A. Dane
    Jones, Adam Leroy
    Moley, Raymond
    Mukherjee, A.M.
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Box 9)
  - Elderfield, Robert C. (Box 9)
  - Elias, Hans (Box 9)
  - 1935-37, 20 items; Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced German Scholars (Box 9-12)
    - 1 letter, from, June 4, 1937; Adler, Cyrus
    - 1 letter, from, Oct. 5, 1937; Beck, Guido, 1903-1988
    - 2 letters, from, 1937; Billikopf, Jacob
    - 1 letter, to, Oct. 13, 1937; Boschwitz, Carl
    - 1 letter, from, July 30, 1937; Brakeley, George A.
    - 1 letter, from, July 15, 1935; Brand, Theodor von
    - 1 letter, from, Oct. 23, 1937; Brandt, Walter
    - 2 letters to and from, Nov. 2 and 3, 1937; Compton, K. T., (Karl Taylor), 1887-1954
    - 1 letter, to, n.d; Courant, R.
    - 12 letters, to and from, 1934-37; Drury, Betty
    - 14 letters, to and from, 1935-37; Duggan, Stephen P.
    - 1 letter, from, August 18, 1936; Ebsen, Annette
    - 1 letter, from, Oct. 5, 1935; Farmer-Loeb, L.
    - 2 letters, to and from, 1936; Farrand, Livingston, 1867-1939
    - 1 letter, to, Dec 21, 1936; Flexner, Bernard (Esq.)
    - 1 letter, July 17, 1937; Flynn, Thomas F (Rev.)
    - 1 letter, from, n.d; Friedrichs, Kurt
    - 2 letters, to and from, SEPT - Oct., 1937; Haskell, Robert H.
    - 2 letters, from, 1937; Hurst, Sandy L.
    - 1 letter, from, July 8, 1937; Hyman, J. C.
    - 1 letter, from, JULE 12, 1937; Jaquith, H. C.
    - 1 letter, from, Nov. 24, 1937; Johnson, Alvin
    - 1 letter, to, Dec. 8, 1936; KC6hler, Wolfgang
    - 1 letter, to, Nov. 15, 1937; Kotschnig, Walter
    - 1 letter, from, n.d.; Lehmann-Hartleben, K.
    - 2 letters, from, 1936; Levy, Fritz
    - 4 letters, to and from, 1936; Mittonzwey, Kuno
    - 2 letters, from, 1935-1937; Murrow, Edward R.
    - 1 letter, from, June 18, 1937; Newton, J. Earle
    - 1 letters, from, 1937; Park, Marion
    - 1 letter, from, Oct. 17, 1937; Reilly, M.
    - 1 letter, to, June 12, 1937; Rosenberg, Jans
    - 1 letter, from, Dec. 2, 1937; Scheerer, Martin
    - 4 letters, to and from, 1935; Stein, Fred M.
    - 1 letter, from, Dec. 3, 1937; Straus, Roger
    - 1 letter, from, Dec. 21, 1936; Warburg, Felix M.
    - 1 letter, from, July 9, 1936; Weissenberg, Richard